One dream, one wish If you want it,
gotta go over the top!
Setting sail and heading for the unknown.
Cutting through the
winds and waves as I go.
Gotta keep it up, never stopping, no.
Cause I'm aiming to get there first, yeah.
It's all or nothing, no time to worry.
Do it later, right now I'm living free.
When your foes look like
they will overwhelm you.
It means your heart's saying
this is what you can't do.
Despite all that to run is not an option.
Once they're closed, I
feel the satisfaction.
You think I'm rude,
here's my appreciation.
When things are getting
tough, just gotta smile.
If you are going on your way.
And you're looking for
a fresh, brand new day.
Then make sure your only
thought you have is.
Yes, I can.
As you're on your way.
Mark maps will be made.
Yes, with every step that you will take.
Just look at all you've been through.
Look ahead at new horizons.
In view shining brightly.
Oh, who knows what's waiting for you.
Dream living, that's the way.
Make like a hurricane.
Now, got to make your mark today.
One dream, one wish.
Your dreams don't run away.
Go for the knockout.
Over the top!
Hey, she's waking up!
It's Big Bro in the Utsuru!
Where am I?
This is my tea house.
Hey, Otama.
So?
Is your stomach feeling all better now?
Is something wrong? Does it still hurt?
No more tummy ache! Yay!
One little sip and that's all it takes?
As they say, the evil purging
herb is a miracle drug.
Takes a bunch, everybody!
Nii-niii!
Nii-niii! Be careful!
Even the medicine can't remove
all of the poison in your body.
So you must not drink
the river water again.
Will you promise me that? Uh-huh!
I learned my lesson good!
Abore your shape!
Quiet tummy!
I need water!
Oden, stop!
What did I just say?
The water, remember?
The river water!
Do not drink it!
There, that should do it.
It's only a field dressing, though.
Looks good.
thanks a ton damn you are
a sizable woman I don't know
compared to big mom she looks
pretty tiny I should have said
thank you for saving me earlier
from that sumo wrestlers
advances I didn't do anything
but look at him I suppose I
introduce myself.
It's a pleasure.
My name is Okiku.
My name?
I can't! No! No way!
I couldn't! I shouldn't!
Take it away! Huh?
I can't!
I don't even have money to pay
for the medicine you gave me!
I can't afford a yummy dessert like this!
Who said you had to pay? It's a gift.
No!
That wouldn't be right!
You and Okiku need to eat!
I know you're as hungry as me!
All is well.
You needn't be shy.
But ma 'am, you already saved my life
and now you're offering me food? No!
It's more than I deserve!
Just take it. Never!
I insist.
I won't take the food and I'll
pay you back for the medicine too!
That's enough out of you!
How did you think this
was going to play out?
I don't want it.
Oh, that's fine, you little imp.
What do you take me for?
Don't want to eat it, do you?
Then how about I go dump
it on the side of the road?
No way!
Otama, please, just eat it.
Otsuru will never back
down from a challenge.
You're just gonna stare at it all day.
Lighten up a little, come on, isn't it?
Supposed to be your birthday?
Oh, is that so?
That's what I heard.
At least good then.
You can consider that a birthday
present from me, so eat up.
Oh, my God.
Yummy!
I had no idea that food
could taste so good!
Huh?
Does that mean you've never
had this stuff before?
Uh-huh!
Do you know how many days it's been
since she's had even a bite to eat?
That poor girl weaves
hats day in and day out.
And if she's lucky, she'll
sell the whole batch,
earning her just enough money to
barely get by and feed herself.
It's even got little mochi balls in it.
This is the feast of a lifetime!
Can't you pull those out of your
cheek whenever you want, though?
Yeah, but you can't fill your
tummy with the ones I make.
No! No!
Hey, lady!
Thank you for being so kind to me!
I've never had such a great birthday!
I don't think I can top it!
A shame that Master isn't
here to share this with me!
Otsuru...
This is the greatest day of my life!
There are children like
her all over this country.
That's the state of things here.
That isn't right.
That poor little kid. Always hungry.
I mean, grown-ups are okay
because we can eat poison.
No, we can't.
You've got the sea, rivers,
and forests, don't you?
There's no reason people
should be starving around here.
That's true.
If only we hadn't destroyed our own land.
Damn, Kaido!
Yeah.
you two are such kind-hearted
young men by the way what are
your names you can call me Zoro
Judo I'm a ronin right I'm monkey
His name is, uh, Luffy Taro.
Huh?
Oh, right.
I'm Luffy Taro.
Honorably.
I know you're from overseas.
I'm surprised that you could make it here.
What gave us away?
I hardly know where to start.
No need to worry.
I won't let your secret out.
I haven't lived in this
town that long myself.
And Okiku has only been working
at my tea house for a month.
I heard the name of this
town means leftovers.
What's the deal with that?
Just like the name implies.
The people here survive on scraps,
specifically from the town where
the government officials live.
Thomas said not all the food here is
poisonous, so where's the good stuff?
Look over there.
Do you see that tall
mountain in the middle?
Lush with foliage and without chimneys?
At its peak, there was once
a place known as Odin Castle.
It's hard to believe so much
time has gone by already.
Odin, huh?
Wait, I know that.
What is it?
Until some 20 years ago,
there was a group called
the Kozuki clan who had
governed this land of
Wano for a very long time.
That vast farm that sits at
the base of the mountain was
constructed by the late Lord Odin
when he watched over this country.
His intent was to provide fresh,
healthy food to everyone in Kuri.
You see how that's turned out.
Now Orochi and his associates
hold everything under their thumb.
The Paradise Farm is beyond our reach.
I heard that.
That food is safe?
Not like the poison stuff here?
That's right.
There's a bounty of crops and fresh
water, clothing, resources, and more.
But we can't so much as gaze upon them.
Not anymore.
They belong to the Shogun Orochi.
On the other side of the Shrine Gate,
there is a town where all
of the officials dwell.
Well,
the people here live off
the scraps that they toss
away and the nearly rotting
food that they sell to us.
Oh, that's why it's called leftovers.
Yes, Okobore, but at least we can live.
Oh, oh,
oh, oh.
What the hell are you doing?
You better stay out of my way.
I heard what you said, woman.
You were speaking ill
of the Shogun just now.
I can hear six times better
than humans like you.
So if anyone trash talks
to Shogun, I'll know.
Regardless of what you might have heard.
There's no excuse to take
someone's life in cold blood.
She would have died if that hit her.
If people keep their mouths
shut then I won't have
to shoot them probably
but if you want to rebel.
Well, that's one thing Lord Orochi
won't stand for no matter what.
What the hell?
You're making me waste all my arrows!
Who are you?
For a couple of weeks now, there
have been robberies at the farm.
We've been looking everywhere for
the criminals without much luck.
Don't tell me.
You're the bandits, aren't you?
A one-eyed ronin.
You're the jerk I saw
on that Wanted poster.
Hmm? Hmm?
Stop it!
Let me go!
What's your deal, weirdo?
Where are you taking her?
Someone help!
Yes!
Taba!
Mission accomplished!
You get back here!
Oh, Kiku!
A sword?
He truly is fast.
I said let's dance!
Shut up, you brat!
I don't give a crap! Mr.
Lionbog, come aid me!
Ah!
Doggy!
That lady has a fancy sword on her.
She did mention that she
knows how to use one.
Though I've never seen her fight.
Hey doggy!
I need a ride too!
Oh, my!
Wait!
I'm coming, too.
Fine!
Are you kidding me?
Lusitaro, thank goodness.
You broke Zoro Judo.
What the heck do they want
from that kid, anyway?
I'm not certain, but we had
better save her quickly.
Huh?
Tama!
I'm coming for you, OK?
Help me!
I got this one.
Just keep going.
Thank you!
So long, losers!
They pulled that off too easily;
they must have been planning this by
order of a headliner, no doubt though.
I know not why, sadly, there's only
one destination in that direction.
They're headed to the town of officials.
What's that?
There are three headliners
that dwell in that town,
hawkins hold 'em and speed.
Indeed.
But that's not all.
There are also about 30
soldiers who acquired
special abilities from
strange artificial fruits.
What is this?
You're more than just a
normal waitress, aren't you?
Start talking.
Hearken well.
I am Samurai.
Hey, Master Hold 'em.
This is Gazelle Man here.
I caught that little brat.
You know?
The one who tamed the
baboon off by the shore.
Someone help me, please!
Excellent work.
We'll put her to good use.
Bring her to me.
Yes, sir!
Big Crow, hurry!
Save me!
In Kuri,
there lies a place known as Bacala Town,
where pirates and officials
flourish while others starve.
That damn rodent!
Who does he think he is?
The powerful aura of his
gave me pause for a moment.
But I'm not giving up on Okiku.
She will be my bride someday, Pin.
I've got status, I've got fame, and
I've got a safe supply of food to eat.
Who could possibly reject
a man like me, Pit?
You gotta stop sweating the
small stuff, you dumb lug.
That gal you fancy's from Okobure Town.
They're so low-class that Lord Orochi won't
even accept them as servants, remember?
Choo-choo-choo-choo!
You're getting hung up on her
feelings when they don't matter.
You can just force her to marry you.
Burn her house down so
she has nowhere to go.
Kill her family so she
has no one to turn to.
Make her completely dependent on you.
When she's starving with
nothing left in the world,
she'll change her tune real fast.
Choo, choo, choo, choo, choo.
You belong to the warrior class.
That distinction means everything in the
land of Wano, so don't be a pushover.
Huh?
You're the star of our national sport,
but you're bowing down
to the whims of a winch.
Show some pride.
It sets a bad example.
That's a fine point.
You're right.
I can do whatever I want with Okiku.
What's the matter?
Was the food not to your liking, sir?
Is that a raccoon dog there?
Yes, it's our pet.
We raised it ourselves.
Why don't you cook it up for me?
Raccoon dog is my favorite food.
You're finally here.
Keep going straight ahead.
We'll charge through the front.
Lifitaro, Zorojuro.
Be ready.
Beyond that gate is Bekori town.
Where officials and pirates reign.
We enter at our own peril.
Now steal thine hearts. You ready?
Always.
You're a tiny little thing.
I almost pity you.
Go ahead and cry if you like.
I'm not gonna cry, you Moon!
Huh?
You trying to act tough?
Ow!
I got a stitch in my side!
I...
Shut up!
Get outta here! Link!
Did you hear me?
Go huff 'n puff somewhere else, would ya?
You're supposed to be a runner, right?
Work on your stamina.
You moron, I wasn't talking to you.
What don't give me that look?
I'm scared!
Why does he have a lie in there?
Wanna fight?
Haven't learned your lesson yet!
What did he just do?
Savage.
That lion always goes
straight for the ball.
Too bad.
Since they share the same body,
it's like the lion is hitting
itself in the balls, too.
It's poetic.
you think you would learn so
this girl here what should we do
with her master holden are you
listening so your name's otama
well you're clearly weak
and a little coward to boot
And yet you tamed that savage baboon!
How'd you do it?
My men saw it happen!
it's too late to play dumb with me we know
it's a Devil Fruit power
but how does it work
Come on, Runt.
Spit it out!
Listen, Otama.
Your unique Devil Fruit ability will
no doubt be enticing to our enemies.
If you use it in front of others,
I fear they may target you.
All right, I'll tell you.
The truth about me is that
I'm real popular with animals.
I don't know why.
Aww.
That is so cute.
And here I thought you had secret powers.
No.
No powers here.
You take me for a fool?
I'm not screwing around here!
Is it your cheek?
That's what they said.
They saw you tear off a piece of it.
If you're not gonna tell me, that's fine.
Let's just try it.
Hey!
Bring me some pliers! Yes, sir!
Not the little ones!
The big scary pair!
Are you there, Big Barrel?
Help me, Big Barrel!
I'm coming, come on!
Turn back, you fools!
Only death awaits you here!
Don't hold back!
If we can just get past
them, we'll have made it!
Luffy, we don't have time
to waste on these chumps.
Push through!
Feed me to it!
Come on, dog! Charge!
Oh no, captain!
There's an emergency.
Do something—you're gonna have to
explain the problem to me first.
So
Straw Hat finally made it to
wanna—that's good—what's the issue?
what's the issue He and Roronoa are
charging straight into Baccona Town,
ready for a fight!
Bunch of fools!
They're going to ruin the whole damn plan!
So it would appear.
What now?
Captain!
Let's go stop them and make it quick!
Go on, Captain!
If you want me to stop then
show me that ability of yours
Dome!
Huh?
How did you do that?
Dock!
Dock?
Conqueror's Haki, they call it!